[Music]  [Applause]  no way the kids are having a sleepover  tonight you don't have to ruin it by  being drunk off your ass  besides we need to go out to buy  manika's axe body spray since we got the  wrong one  what are you saying [ __ ] edward is way  better than jacob that's why bella  picked him  well i'm saying she made a mistake  jacob is clearly the better boyfriend  than that sparkling pretty boy [ __ ]  boyfriend  they were never even dating to begin  with doesn't matter what you think you  god dang [ __ ] because edward won either  way  you're just salty how dare you  you dare disrespect me in my own home  get the hell off me sonic you better let  go of your sister right now  [Music]  that is enough  what in the world has gotten into you  kids  stop  said stop it you fat [ __ ]  we just got done watching twilight  breaking dawn  it was his first time and now he won't  quit saying jacob is better than edward  only because he is  mom  uncle chuck you two are on team jacob  right tell her she's wrong  i'm almost 17 years old  so primera don't know if it's ripped  formatted the water where it works are  intense  sparky no folks are intense  you sure you got everything pumpkin  i don't mind heading back to the house  if you need something  oh daddy you're such a worry what for  the last time yes  oh you know me sugar just got to look  out for my girl  daddy you don't need to worry it's just  a slumber party at my friend's house  like come on i mean really what's the  worst that could happen  i don't like that tone young lady  you are my girl aren't you  say it say it loud and clean  yeah yeah i am i'm your precious baby  girl daddy  that's it say it for daddy you dirty  [ __ ]  little [ __ ] [ __ ]  [Music]  i i'm gonna head out  if you need anything just give me a call  so this is the place where we're going  to have the slumber party my bitch's  house how sad it's so small i bet it  only cost 89 trillion dollars but i  guess that's how it goes  thankfully i'm not a judging person  i simply cannot wait to see my bitch's  face like when he sees that i brought  him the limited edition drink a borja  blast from taco bell  he'll be so excited i bet he'll even  suck my balls or should i say suck my  burrito how  hey [ __ ] open the door and tuck on my  penis  not showing up i see i guess you like  playing hard to get that's fine by me  should i just blow down the door with  nothing but my [ __ ] piss again  wow the way  is that a blast from taco bell  can i have one no way piss off  go get your own these are for me and my  beak  oh god damn it look what you've done you  broke my concentration and made me pee  in my baja blast  well at least now i know which one my  [ __ ] is getting  knuckles bartleby you're just in time me  and my bro were just getting done  preparing snacks for tonight's sleepover  how are you ready for a night with just  the guys  you bet and look i brought you a little  surprise  a wonderful guy blast from taco bell  oh bartelby you treat me so well  if there's one thing that i can't say  for certainty it's that high sonic the  hedgehog really love the limited edition  drink aha blast from taco bell  [ __ ] who are you talking to  let's go upstairs to my room me and  manic rented this really pick-ass game  from blockbuster  okay  hey mindy what do you wanna do first the  other girls didn't arrive yet but i'm  sure we can't still find ways to have  fun  sonia what is going on here  i thought you invited 12 other girls  where is everyone you're the only one  who showed up so far i'm sure they'll  get here eventually  but i'm seven hours late  i got an idea let's facetime everyone  and see what's going on  maybe they're just stuck in traffic  somewhere  we'll try calling sari first since she  seemed most excited and [ __ ]  [Music]  why howdy there sonja how are you doing  this evening sorry i took so long to  answer your call  i was just busy sucking paws balls i  mean i was just busy helping my  boyfriend chair emma farm  you know bundling hay and whatnot i  definitely wasn't cheating on him with  his pro or anything  where the hell are you [ __ ]  sarah the reason we called you was to  figure out if you're still on for the  sleepover tonight  that was tonight holy moly i forgot  entirely about that no i'm not coming  over  i'll try and make it up to you next time  by bringing my delicious home down  macaroni salad it's a real treat  [Music]  how's it hanging well besides all of  these guys balls over here at the local  strike club haha  mundy why are you at the strip mall when  you've been planning the slumber party  for weeks  more importantly why didn't you take me  with you  [Music]  sarah who's that behind you  yeah what oh you must have seen jared we  just got done having steamy sex out in  the pasture  no i'm i'm pretty sure that was jars  paul  [Music]  sarah paw you in there  thought you were being real sneaky going  out to the barn behind my back don't you  well i'm not stupid  and no luck can guard you against my  rage  [Music]  come on out and get yours paw i told you  what would happen if i caught you  [ __ ] my girl again i'm gonna blow  your brains out  i think i'm gonna get going you girls  have fun now yeah  here sarah shut that [ __ ] camera off  cause i'm gonna rape your ass  so long you too i gotta get back to work  if i stay on this vid too long the  police will find out my location later  [ __ ]  okay kids we're leaving for the store  remember to keep all the doors locked up  and don't forget to go to bed at nine if  it gets too cold turn up the thermostat  in the hall  do you think the kids will be okay by  themselves maybe one of us should stay  back just in case  it's finesses  the kids are old enough to take care of  themselves  and besides bart levy is so strong i can  lift a monster to quick these boot  checks  you made a huge mistake challenging  knuckles the cool kidney to a game of  twister everybody knows i'm the king  when it comes to board games  yeah well you're gonna see who's really  the king of twister tonight let's make a  bet then [ __ ] loser owes the other one  five bucks  manic left hand green  [Music]  sorry knux i should have told you why it  is spicy bean and cheese burrito this  morning haha  ha ha you should warn the guy before you  go and do stuff like that that [ __ ] was  stinky  is this really what poor people do at  sleep of us well i guess it is on the  guy the type printed off from the poor  person's wikipedia page but they're  doing everything out of order this is  all just so confusing to me  hey [ __ ] what time are we going to have  the pillow fight  a pillow fight um i don't think we were  planning on having a pillow fight my bro  and i only have a couple pillows so it  wouldn't be possible since there's four  of us but my guide says poor people do  that  well pillow fights are more of a girl's  thing i see so only poor females  participate in pillow fights  i was really looking forward to that too  [ __ ] can you tell me where the bathroom  in your houses so that i may go poop  it's moments like this where i can  plainly see that i am different from  everybody else  i'm different from everybody i'm weird  all because i'm the richest man on earth  it's not like it's anything new either  from the very beginning i have suffered  under this burden  hey bartleby you know today is my  birthday the rest of the class are  coming over to my place after school for  a huge sleepover there's going to be  cake and ice cream too and solar sticks  with peanut butter you got big muscles  and i also hear you're the richest kid  in school i think that's kind of cool  do you want to come to my sleepover i've  got an extra invitation  dude what the hell are you doing why  would you give an invite to bart libby  everybody knows he's the weird kid he's  different from the rest of us  that's right i hear his family is so  rich that his dab threat and to buy the  entire school if any of the teachers  even dare to give bart levy anything  lower than an a-plus  if i were you i'd be scared to be  friends with someone who has that much  power you know what you guys are right  barnaby you're not invited to my  sleepover anymore you're a freak a  monster  come one let's go see if they're serving  chicken nuggets in the cafeteria today  [Music]  is  [Music]  can anybody make me feel  [Music]  oh sorry [ __ ] i didn't know you are out  here what do you want  bart levy my beautiful lover i heard you  singing all the way from down the hall  tell me honestly are you not having fun  at my sleepover  i'm so sorry if it's not to your  satisfaction  you don't have to apologize my [ __ ]  it's not your fault your sleeper sucks  big sweaty balls you know i just  struggle to fit in with you poor people  and your poor people activities oh my  god peeing in poor people's bathrooms is  so boring there's not even a roller  coaster or a butler to give you a warm  towel and a small bottle of soap after  you're done  oh would you look at the time it's  almost 9pm didn't your mom say it's  lights off at nine we should hurry to  bed  where do i [ __ ] go i don't have a key  for the door i don't know try punching  that [ __ ]  ha ha ha it worked yeah i just don't  know why edmund is following you around  like that maybe he's [ __ ] gay i think  he's peter's younger brother i know but  he could still be homosexual  [Music]  sonic are you [ __ ] [ __ ] dear god  what is wrong with you we were just  playing the chronicles of narnia for the  playstation 2.  yeah bro have you lost your marbles this  game doesn't even ought to save  but bro it's nine o'clock and mama said  we all have to be in bed by nine your  mom isn't even here she want out  remember  we have two knucks our mom always says  good kids go to bed on time  manic you can be such a square sometimes  you know that  good night knuckles  good night bart libby  i'm sorry you have to sleep on the floor  babe there's just not enough space in  the bunk bed for all four of us and well  with me being the thick little boy that  i am i take up a whole bed myself  don't worry about it my [ __ ] i wouldn't  be caught dead sleeping in a poor  person's bed anyway i'm just fine and  dandy sleeping in my solid gold sleeping  bag that cost 906 trillion dollars night  bro i guess i'll see you in the morning  now hold on a mobius minute bro aren't  you forgetting something  you know that special thing the two of  us do just before bed every night  [Music]  well what are you waiting for bring it  on in here my special baby bro  [Music]  haha what is it little bro you look like  you're thinking about something really  hard  it's nothing big bro nothing at all i'm  just really happy right now  it's just been so long since mom let us  have a sleepover you know i had fun  today  [Music]  okay okay that's enough row quit  breathing down my neck it tickles  oh come on bro can't i keep my arms  around you for just a little bit longer  [Music]  knocks knuckles  hey hey knuckles are you awake  manic what do you want can't you see  it's almost one in the morning  i was just having a really awesome dream  where i was drinking root beer and  eating cookies  i'm hungry let's go downstairs and sneak  some food out of the fridge  no i want to go back to sleep  come on knucks my mom just bought some  macaroni i'll make you some of my world  famous manic and cheese  what the [ __ ] is mannequin cheese  it's just kraft macaroni and cheese but  my bro thinks his is special because he  adds green food coloring  i call it mannequin cheese because it's  green like me  manic just go back to bed we're trying  to sleep  huh bro where did you go  what are you doing my bro  yo everybody you're just in time for  some of my world-famous mannequin cheese  how about you all pull up the seat i'm  about to rock your world with this  cheesy [ __ ]  all that's left for me to do is to add  the secret ingredient  okay bro go easy on the green food color  ring you know how much that [ __ ] costs  if you run out mom's gone a beepist but  beach it's just a tiny bottle of food  coloring i mean how much could it cost  fifty six thousand dollars  open your mouth beach here comes the  chewy shoot rain  [Applause]  hey sonja it looks like your mom and  uncle are home  but mindy that doesn't really look like  my mom's car  yo bobby moonbeam you made sure to scope  this place out before right you sure  there's nobody inside  i'm not about to be caught and spend  four more years in prison i've done my  time  i'm positive about this house [ __ ] i  saw the family carl leave a couple hours  ago the place is empty  big brother are you sure you want to do  this you have always told me stealing is  wrong what happened to you it's like  ever since you met bobby moonbeam you've  changed  cindy you know mom and ted have the  coronavirus because they were  anti-massacres if we don't find a way to  get money we'll never be able to afford  their vaccines and hospital bills  there are plenty of other ways to get  money take me back to the strip club and  i'll show you i make six dollars a day  cindy i told you six dollars is nothing  just mods hospital bills alone are eight  thousand bucks  sorry to interrupt your little solid  story but are we going to get down to  business or what  sorry bobby moonbeam i got distracted  what's the plan i will tell you the plan  but first the screen  has got to pass some gas out of his ass  okay let's get out of the car i'll tell  you the plan when we get up by the  driveway  okay here is the plan  we're going to get that door open and  when you do the three of us rush in and  steal [ __ ]  if we coming across any live forms let  me know immediately so i can kill them  bobby movie wants to be out there in 10  minutes or less  don't worry bobby we'll be in and out of  there before anybody even know what  happened let's get going  butternuts the door is locked body keep  your eyes open for on lickers i'm going  to use my pistol to blow the log  what's that do you got a better idea  we shall use my alien ring it released a  special frequency so high that it cannot  be picked up by earthlings  it is said that manitoba himself took  one of these models into the final  battle against doctor robotnik  and then he used it to blow robotics  closed clean off and then  bobby why are you the only one i ever  hear that story from i'm starting to  think you make [ __ ] up as you go along  [Applause]  [Music]  hey does anyone hear that loud ringing  sound  i think it's coming from outside what do  you think it is  some kind of weird emergency alarm  it's not an alarm you idiot it's an  alien ray from mobius  but how  i thought all alien rays were lost when  mobius fell  they were until today that is somehow  one ended up in this very neighborhood  perhaps it's a mobian who came looking  for revenge since the hedgehog royal  family failed them  you guys there's a group of weirdos out  front i think someone's trying to break  in  bart levy i'm frightened  what do we do  everyone scatter it's every man for  himself  that's not alien food body moon bean i'm  pretty sure that it's just mac and  cheese with green food coloring poured  on top  if what you're seeing is true then it  must mean there are life forms somewhere  in the house let's split up and find  them  cindy you're going stairs and check out  there rodnick you stay here in the  kitchen and have a look around  while are you doing i'm going to take a  big [ __ ] double toilet  good luck bro if you need anything just  call i'll be right there  yo manic what are we going to do  there's no way we can make to the front  door like this  i don't know i got the police on the  phone right now maybe we should try the  window  good idea [ __ ] let's do it to it  knuckles watch out for the  [Music]  [Music]  oh no i'm stuck  knuckles pull me hurry up  i can't get my fat ass through the  window god why do i have to be related  to sonic the hedgehog  just hold tight man i got you  that was a warning shot red boy now get  the foot out of here unless you want me  to pop a cap in your butt  now that we're alone it's time  no  please don't kill me i'll do anything  tell you who said anything about killing  you i'm just gonna [ __ ] you [ __ ]  you know what i wanna enjoy this you  stay right here i'm going out front and  i'll meet you outside so you can see my  balls  see you in a moment beep  this is the police put your hands up  you're under arrest [ __ ]  [Music]  bartleby i'm scared he has a gun what  are we going to do  hurry up and shut that hole under your  nose if you don't make a sound he won't  find us  don't think i didn't hear that i know  there's someone hiding behind the shower  curtain  coming out right now or else i'm going  to rip your balls off with my teeth god  damn it [ __ ] you and your planet-sized  butt cheeks  i don't get screams of the innocent  perhaps i was wrong and there's nobody  after all  wow bart levy you caught every single  one of the bullets in your bare hands  how did you manage to do that haha we've  been over this remember i'm even faster  than you [ __ ] yes even faster than  sonic the hedgehog himself  who are you what the hell are you  choking me with [ __ ]  these are my panties i hope you don't  mind that they're covered in my [ __ ]  pee  sonia harry grab the hammer that i  shoved up my big smelly ass five minutes  ago break this bitch's legs  [Music]  i will take that kind of your hands  hurry up and kill her mindy i'm going to  call the police  no sonia i'm going to enjoy this  i want her death to be slow and painful  [Music]  i think somebody was hiding behind the  shower curtain wall i was pooping you'll  find your brother we're gonna make like  a bunch of bananas and peel out  what the hell is going on here cindy get  up get a piece of the [ __ ] you killed  her you [ __ ] killed her didn't you  i've heard stories about you bobby  moonbeam they say you're the most evil  alien criminal in the galaxy but also  one of the most cowardly and most stupid  i batlaby montler of raised in the  richest and sexiest man on earth will  make you pay for ruining my bitch's  special sleepover prepare yourself you  little green major boy  [ __ ] if i had known that this was the  house of barnaby's personal [ __ ] sorry  i would never have come here  i didn't spill anything yet if you let  me go i promise don't even never come  back please please forgive me  you want forgiveness find religion  hey bart levy do you know what's funny  in a way it seems you did get your  pillow fight after all  hey you're right it looks like i did and  i even had fun too  bobby moonbeam you are under arrest for  136 counts of galactic murder and home  invasion your friend rodnick here told  us everything so don't even try running  away you naughty little alien boy  hey kids  where are you back  and look whoever broke pisa  hey [ __ ] now that this mess is over  with how about we start this sleepover  for realest  yet i think that sounds quite nice  then what's the holdup let's go have a  hot and ready ham and pineapple pizza  for only five dollars from little  [Music]  caesars building a brighter light where  no one knows  [Music]  where dreams  [Music]  you